Finding Aid for Michigan Bell Telephone Company Photographs 1949-1983
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Release forms (Box 93)
Centennial celebrations -- 293, 567, 575-576, 582, 583, 588, 589
Cherry Festival (Traverse City, Mich.) -- 587
Chickens -- 286
Children -- 549, 551, 622, 626
Children and phones -- 92
Children singing -- 93
Children's parties -- 97-101, 230, 231
Chris Craft Company -- 500
Christmas -- 95-101, 230, 231
Christmas decorations 95, 95-a
Christmas dolls -- 96
Churches -- 102
Civil Defense -- 117
Cobo Hall (Detroit, Mich.) -- 192
Coin collectors -- 118, 369
Community service -- 311
Compressors -- 125
Computers -- 5, 127-128, 169
Concentrator cable -- 129
Conduits - Laying -- 131
Confectioneries -- 542
Construction -- 324, 493
Construction - Michigan Bell Bldg. -- 50, 53-58
Cookery -- 318
Country life -- 529-531
Curling -- 599
Customer relations -- 134
Customs inspections -- 545
Dataphone (also equipment TWX) -- 168, 256
Data processing See Computers
Dataspeed -- 170
Demonstrations (telephone equipment, displays, etc.) -- 171-174 (See also Displays; Publicity; Window displays, Open houses)
Detroit Builder's Show -- 193
Detroit (Mich.) - Buildings -- 45-65, 105-107, 465-468
Detroit Civic Center -- 105
Detroit Historical Museum -- 194
Detroit Institute of Arts -- 177
Detroit Metropolitan Airport -- 178
Detroit News Want Ads Department, 1951 -- 259
Detroit (Mich.) - Riot, 1967 -- 528
Detroit River -- 42
Detroit (Mich.) - Streets -- 571
Detroit Tigers (baseball team) -- 596
Detroit (Mich.) - Views -- 45-49, 105-107
Detroit Zoological Park (Mich.) -- 500
DEW Line -- 13
Diesel power -- 492
Dining rooms -- 184
Dining services -- 184
Disasters -- 136-165
Displays -- 190-220
Dolls -- 96
Dwellings -- 323-324
Electric Switching System (ESS) -- 226
Electronic Secretary -- 227
Employment Office -- 244
Engineers -- 250-251
Excavations for conduits -- 131
Exhibitions -- 190-205
Explosions -- 136
Fairs -- 195-198, 284
Families -- 285
Farming -- 11, 529-531, 650
Farms - Chicken hatchery -- 286
Fashion shows -- 287
Fiber optics -- 288
Fire alarms -- 14
Fires -- 137-142, 290
First aid -- 291
Fishing -- 600
Flat Rock (Mich.) -- 136, 150
Flint, Mich. -- 108, 161, 292
Flint Journal -- 400
Floods -- 143
Flowers -- 294
Food -- 295
Football -- 601
Ford Motor Company (plant and headquarters) -- 30, 296-297
Fort Custer -- 299
Fort Wayne -- 300
4-H clubs -- 301
Frankenmuth (Mich.) -- 410
Fred W. Sanders Company (Detroit, Mich.) -- 542
Furniture -- 574
Garroway, Dave -- 670
General Motors -- 139, 307
General Motors Corporation. Buick Motor Division -- 30
Girl Scouts -- 309
Golf -- 232, 602
Goodwill Industries -- 501
Grand Marais (Mich.) -- 404
Grand Rapids (Mich.) -- 109, 162, 574
Greenfield Village -- 104
Grocery stores -- 616
Grosse Isle U.S. Naval Air Base -- 312
Handicapped persons -- 314, 369
Health care -- 38
Hearing aids -- 315
Hillsdale (Mich.) -- 151, 162
Hobbies -- 2, 6, 7, 232-234, 316-317, 474-481, 497-499, 690
Holland (Mich.) -- 110, 152
Horner Woolen Company -- 500
Horseback riding -- 320
Horses -- 320
Hospitals - Battle Creek -- 321-322
Hotels and taverns -- 267, 501
Houghton (Mich.) -- 111
Houses see Dwellings
Hudsonville (Mich.) -- 163
Hunting -- 537
Hurricanes -- 145
Huts (Telephone) -- 325
Hyatt Regency (Detroit, Mich.) -- 64
Ice Hockey -- 603
Iceboating -- 669
Independent telephone companies -- 326
Inkster (Mich.) -- 324
Ionia (Mich.) -- 115
Jack and plug -- 338
Janitors -- 44
Junior Achievement -- 339-342
Kalamazoo (Mich.) -- 112
Kappel, Frederick -- 343
Kennedy, John F. -- 491
Kitchens, 184, 318
Labor -- 132, 136-165, 222, 251, 644
Labor negotiations -- 618, 710
Labor unions -- 617-620, 710
Lansing (Mich.) -- 113, 140
Law and legal affairs, 346-347
Law offices -- 346
Leisure -- 716 -- See also Hobbies
Lighthouses -- 349
Lincoln Park (Mich.) -- 159
Linemen see Telephone - Linemen
Lotteries -- 353
Lounges -- 354
Mackinac Bridge (Mich.) -- 43
Mackinac, Straits of -- 43, 70
Mackinaw City (Mich.) -- 70
Magic -- 10
Manhole covers -- 361
Manistee (Mich.) -- 114
Marion (Mich.) -- 115
Medicine -- 38, 321-322, 370-371
Message registers -- 372
Michigan Bell Building (Detroit, Mich.) -- 45-62, 721
Michigan - Capitol Building -- 113
Michigan. Constitutional Convention (1961-1962) -- 570
Michigan - Scenic views -- 546-547
Michigan State Fair -- 197
Michigan State Police -- 489-490
Michigan State University - Campus -- 579
Michigan State University - Commencement, 1963 -- 343
Michigan Week -- 580
Microphones -- 373
Microwave horns -- 374
Microwave towers -- 375-377
Military Communications Autovon -- 378
Military life -- 299-300, 398, 522, 555, 560
Missiles -- 380-381
Mobile Central Office -- 382
Mobile homes -- 693
Mobile radio telephone -- 383-386
Mobile switchboards -- 387
Mobile telecoach -- 388
Money -- 369
National Bank of Detroit -- 263
National Guard -- 398, 528
Newspapers -- 400
Nike missile -- 380-381
Northland Shopping Center -- 405
Nurses -- 370-371
Oak Park (Mich.) -- 141
Occupations [throughout]
Office equipment [throughout]
Office workers -- throughout, esp. 243, 407, 506-511, 553, 558-559, 703, 708
Offices -- 406
Open houses -- 408-420, 685-687
Paintings -- 438-461
Parades and processions -- 293, 463, 571, 587, 589, 621
Percy Jones Hospital (Battle Creek, Mich.) -- 322
Photographers -- 512
Physicians -- 370-371
Pickets -- 617-619
Pickles -- 501
Pinsetters -- 598
Plant training -- 485-487
Playboy Bunny -- 189
Plymouth (Mich.) -- 115
Pole hole digger -- 488, 644
Police -- 489-490
Political conventions -- 134
Politicians -- 491
Port Huron (Mich.) -- 164, 545
Printing industry -- 494
Prison facilities - Michigan - Jackson -- 495
PBX -- 496-501, 634
Princess Phones 504-505(2 folders)
Publicity -- 189-220, 379, 388
Racquet ball -- 605
Radar -- 513
Radio Relay Stations -- 514
Radioisotopes -- 517
Rapcon Relay Rack -- 518
Refugees -- 188
Renaissance Center (Detroit, Mich.) -- 106, 179
Republican National Convention (Detroit, Mich.), 1980 -- 133
Retirement -- 525-526
Ringing Machines -- 527
Riot - Michigan - Detroit 1967 -- 528
River Rouge (Mich.) -- 156
Rockets -- 380-381
Royal Oak (Mich.) -- 165, 465, 583
Safety -- 1, 532-540
Saginaw (Mich.) -- 116
Sailboats -- 42, 606
Sailing -- 606
St. Ignace (Mich.) -- 70, 135
Sales, Soupy -- 670
Salk polio vaccine announcement -- 584
Salt mining - Michigan -- 114
Schools -- 549-551, 622
Sculpture - Alexander Calder -- 62-63
Seasons -- 552
Secretaries see Office workers
Selfridge Air Force Base -- 555
Service Action Force -- 556
Ships -- 42, 561
Shopping centers -- 198, 405
Signal towers -- 375-377
Signs -- 562-563
Singing -- 310
Skiing -- 2, 539, 607
Soap box derby -- 608
Soda fountains -- 542
Solar batteries -- 564
Southfield (Mich.) - Buildings -- 65
Splicers -- 592
Sports -- 593-612
Square dancing -- 166
Stained glass -- 102
Standale (Mich.) -- 163
State Prison of Southern Michigan -- 495
Stocks -- 613-615
Storms -- 149-157
Strikes -- 617-621, 710
Students 622-626
Submarine cables -- 69-70, 78
Swimming -- 609
Switchboards see Telephone - Switchboards
Table tennis -- 610
Telephone -- 120
Telephone booths -- 118
Telephone cables -- 68-80, 131
Telephone - Card dialer -- 85
Telephone - Dataphone -- 168, 256, 660
Telephone - Defense measures -- 13, 117
Telephone - Design Line -- 175-176
Telephone, Dial -- 85
Telephone directories -- 368
Telephone - Employees -- 68, 75, 82, 167, 181, 185-186, 235-236, 238-241, 292, 328-333, 350-352, 402-403, 494, 523, 627-630, 675-679, 691
Telephone - Equipment and supplies -- 71-73, 81, 89, 124, 132, 180, 185, 228-229, 255-282, 302-306, 335-336, 681
Telephone etiquette -- 697
Telephone - Historical -- 334
Telephone Hour -- 515, 642-643
Telephone - Installation -- 259-267, 328-333
Telephone - Installation in homes -- 222
Telephone - Key cabinets -- 344
Telephone - Linemen -- 350-352, 529-531
Telephone lines -- 68-80
Telephone lines - Underground [71-72, 80]
Telephone - Magicall -- 355
Telephone - Manufacture of -- 726-729
Telephone - Mobile radio telephone -- 383-386
Telephone operators -- 82, 235, 298, 421-434
Telephone - Panel phone -- 462
Telephone - Picture phone -- 484
Telephone planned home -- 493
Telephone poles -- 488, 644
Telephone Princess Phone -- 504-505
Telephone - Public Telephones -- 464-473
Telephone - Radio telephone -- 645
Telephone - Rapidial -- 85, 265
Telephone - Repair -- 729
Telephone - Repairmen -- 523
Telephone - Repeater -- 524
Telephone - Ship to shore -- 561
Telephone - Speaker hones -- 565
Telephone switchboards -- 497-501, 632-634
Telephone switching systems, Electronic -- 130, 226, 302-306, 485-487, 635-637
Telephone systems -- 302-306
Telephone systems - Carrier systems -- 87
Telephone - Teleprinter -- 657
Telephone - Teletypewriter -- 658-660
Telephone - Time Service -- 680
Telephone - Toll dialing -- 681
Telephone - Touch-a-matic -- 683
Telephone - Touchtone -- 684
Telephone - Training in schools -- 625
Telephone - Transaction Phone -- 698
Telephone - Trimline -- 705-706
Telephone wire -- 730
Teletypewriters -- 658-660
Television industry -- 661-672
Telstar (communications satellite) -- 544
Tennis -- 611
Terminals (terminal shelters) -- 673
Thom, Robert (artist) -- 438-461
Tools -- 682
Tornadoes -- 158-165
Towers -- 375-377, 688
Traffic accidents -- 1
Transistors -- 700
Transportation -- 237, 701
Traverse City (Mich.) -- 587
Tree trimming -- 704
Trucks -- 390-396
Turbines -- 492
Turkey farming -- 11
Uniforms -- 709
United Foundations -- 711-712
Universities and colleges -- 119
University of Michigan. Stadium -- 331
Visible Speech Machine -- 722
Vocational education -- 485-487, 694-696
Volleyball -- 612
Vorhees, Donald -- 642-643
Voting -- 225
WWJ-TV (Detroit, Mich.) -- 672
Weddings -- 725
Western Electric -- 726-729
Window displays -- 204-205, 208-209, 212-220
Winter -- 146-147, 150-152, 155, 157, 404, 552
Women -- [throughout]
Women athletes -- 597
World War II - Homefront -- 2, 715
Wurtsmith Air Force Base -- 734
Wyandotte (Mich.) -- 589
Youth -- 339-342